article-s.co.uk 2012-05-14

# Privacy Policy | Articles Directory

## Privacy Policy

## Your Privacy

Here we are to protect your privacy. The purpose of this notice is to let you know about our online information commitments and the alternatives that you may opt for the way your information is collected and used. We also try to make this notice easy to access by displaying it on our homepage and at other places where you can request for the information.

### Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google serves to be a third party advertisement vendor that provides ads on the site with the help of cookies. Google uses DART cookies to avail advertisements to the visitors that depend on how much they visit to this website or the other sites on the Web.

The following URL can be visited to avail the DART cookies to visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

Tracking of users is done through a DART cookie mechanism which is under Google’s privacy policies. These cookies are also used by the Third Party ad servers or ad networks to track users’ utility on this website to measure effectiveness of adverts and other reasons that will be provided in the privacy policies of their own. The third party advertisers with the use of these cookies have no right to publish articles on Article-S.

### Collection of Personal Information

When you visit [www.article-s.co.uk](http://www.article-s.co.uk/), the IP address with which you access the site will be logged on, providing the date and time of your accession. The information conducted is used only to analyze trends, administer the site, collect broad demographic information for internal use and track users’ movement. Also, if anyone accesses with the recorded IP addresses then the personal identifiable information will not be retrieved.

### Links to Third Party Websites

Further links are also provided on this website for your use and reference, but Articles-S will not be take responsibility of the privacy policies of those links. One must take care of the privacy policies of these sites as you may find them different from those of our website.

### Changes to This Privacy Statement

The content is subjected to be changed anytime by our website. For any queries regarding the privacy policy of Articles-S, please feel free to contact us at [www.article-s.co.uk](http://www.article-s.co.uk/)
